# rameşaliyev

#### **Full Stack Developer**

I'm an experienced web based full-stack software engineer who ♥ javascript, frontend, backend, devops, functional programming, math, geometry and machine learning. Please visit my personal website ramesaliyev.com and other profiles to get further information about my experimental works.

### experiences

Senior Full Stack Developer @ OmmaSign Sep 2018 - Present

Co-Founder & Full Stack Developer @ Ecma Co. Ltd. Jun 2017 - Present

Senior Frontend Developer @ Pisano Feb 2018 - Sep 2018 (8 months)

Senior Full Stack Developer @ Emlakjet Jan 2016 - Oct 2017 (1 year 10 months)

Senior JavaScript Developer (Consultant) @ Turkcell Oct 2013 - Dec 2015 (2 years 3 months)

JavaScript Developer @ E-NET Internet Technology Co Jan 2013 - Sep 2013 (9 months)

Frontend Developer @ Techpoint Labs Mar 2012 - Jan 2013 (11 months)

Full Stack Developer @ Koridor Prodüksiyon ve Tasarım Atölyesi Feb 2009 - Mar 2012 (3 years 2 months)

### education

Yildiz Technical University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Engineering · (2018 - 2022)

Sakarya University
Associate's Degree, Computer Programming (2016 - 2018)

Zeytinburnu Industrial Vocational High School High School, Electronic Technology/Technician · (2004 - 2007)

## volunteer experience

Trainer @ Frontend Camp'17 Summer Aug 2017

Organiser / Speaker @ JSNinjas - Free For All Aug 2015

Speaker @ The Frontiers:Mini Jun 2015

#### links

ramesaliyev.com
github.com/ramesaliyev
linkedin.com/in/ramesaliyev
twitter.com/ramesaliyev

#### contact

creator@ramesaliyev.com